zurvita.com 2015-03-24

# STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

    STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
 Our Commitment to Privacy
Our Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality
products and services with integrity in dealing with users. The Policy is designed to assist you in
the understanding of how we collect, use and protect the personal information provided to us.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our site, we collect two types of information: personal information you actively
choose to disclose ("Active Information") and Use information collected, in a way not visible to
you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and other users browse our site ("Passive
Information").
1. Personally Identifiable Information
This refers to information that lets us know specifically about you i.e. profile information.
A. Registration
When you register to become an authorized reseller of our products or services, we will collect
Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone
number). This Personally Identifiable Information is securely stored and may be accessed on our
website. You are assigned an identification number and select your own password - both are
needed to enter the Site and to access your Contact Information. Please safeguard your password
in a secure location as we are not responsible for breaches into the system when access is
willingly provided.
B. Ordering
When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information
(such as name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transactional information).
We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate the status of
your order.
C. Credit Card Storage
Credit card information collected at registration or for product orders is used only to process
payment for the transaction and, generally, is not retained on our Site. However, you may
voluntarily elect to securely store multiple credit cards to be used for product orders.
D. Surveys and Promotions
Occasionally, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete
surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our
                                       Zurvita | WEBSITE_PRIVACY_POLICY_EN_20140612          1

    STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
products and services and to ensure that we're providing accurate disclosures. We may also use
your Personally Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing
information that coincide with your preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences,
or let us know if you do not wish to receive any promotional materials, by adjusting your
Subscriptions & Email options on the Site.
2. Aggregate Information
This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such
information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website that referred
you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your
computer whenever you surf the web), your operating system and browser type, and any search
terms that you enter on our Site. Our web server aggregates this information in order to monitor
the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content or our Site in
order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.
We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any
Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do
not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we
collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like
any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.
Active Information You Choose to Provide
In order to gain use of the site (become a "user"), we require you to disclose the following
information: Name, Address and Phone Number.
We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you
submit to us when you use our secure online forms. The information you provide to us is stored
securely.
Passive Information Collected
What is a Cookie?
Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer
used to access a site. They are small pieces of data stored by a user's browser to simplify
subsequent interactions with the site. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and
to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier
and more personalized.
Our site utilizes cookies to collect information about how our site is used. Passive Information
gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the
sites visited just before and just after visiting our site. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie"
information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser.
                                      Zurvita | WEBSITE_PRIVACY_POLICY_EN_20140612              2

   STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
Our site's servers also automatically identify you computer by its Internet Protocol address, which
is a unique string of numbers that are assigned to your computer by your Internet Service
Provider. The IP address may be used to address problems with our server or to gather broad
demographic information about our users. We passively collect your IP Address.
How Do We Use the Information Collected?
Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction use
Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer
support and making available other products or services we think might be of interest to our
users. We may use the Active Information or Passive Information you provide to contact you
about various changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer. If at any time you
do not wish to receive such information, you may "opt-out" of doing so by adjusting your email
settings in the back office of the website.
We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance our site to
make it easier, faster and friendlier for users. Additionally, cookies help us better understand the
usage pattern of the people that visit our site, which helps us improve our services. Passive
Information may result in your viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits.
Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To
You might be able to access other websites through our site via hyperlinks. When you do so, you
are subjecting yourself to their privacy policies and data collection. Please read the privacy
policies of those sites to ensure you agree with the terms before using such sites.
Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties
We may disclose anonymous information about user habits to advertisers on our site. The parties
who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant bank, Internet Service Provider)
may also have access to your information in performing such services. Should we buy or sell
assets of our company, another company may need to review our company's assets, which might
include your information, to make business decisions as to whether to acquire such assets.
Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law
We may be required by subpoena, law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive
Information you have provided to us.
How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?
We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent
unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss of Active and Passive Information.
Individual postings on this site and other communications to our office via email or standard mail
                                     Zurvita | WEBSITE_PRIVACY_POLICY_EN_20140612             3

    STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your
submission of information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these
means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we respectfully request that you do not send or
post sensitive information through these means.
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on
our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or
otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information provided to us, you may edit your
information online.
Protecting Your Information
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally
Identifiable Information provided from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ
physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.
It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site and to promptly
advise us if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage
you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your
identification number and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for
any and all use of our Site conducted with your identification number and password.
Links to Other Websites
Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience or to
provide additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and
Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not
cover the information practices of those websites nor do we control their content or privacy
policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Children's Privacy Protection
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an
active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for
children under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable
Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our site, we will
eliminate that data. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting:
http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm.
                                      Zurvita | WEBSITE_PRIVACY_POLICY_EN_20140612              4

   STATEMENT OF WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
Changes to This Statement
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted on our Site and the
date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you
submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has
changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at
the time of use.
YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS THAT YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN
THIS POLICY. YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE
CHANGES.
                                   Zurvita | WEBSITE_PRIVACY_POLICY_EN_20140612             5
